Green Dolphin Street Prison.
Also known as "The Aquarium."
At some point in time,
it had birthed mystery and power.
Something unseen by ordinary men.
Power and mystery drenched in filth.
PUNISHMENT WARD
Jolyne got five added years
for her jailbreak and has been in
the Punishment Ward for a few weeks.
Everything will start afterward...
Everything.
INFIRMARY WARD
Before that, I must investigate something.
It concerns another inmate.
Her name is…
Ermes Costello.
Jolyne has already met her.
Hey! What the hell
do you think you're doing?
Hey! I'm talking to you, bastard!
Is this...
the infirmary?
EPISODE 6: ERMES'S STICKERS
Shit! That was the bathroom janitor.
That was my hard-earned money.
Dammit!
Oh, I'm starting to remember now.
I hurt my right palm.
I had a fever too.
But my hand is almost completely healed.
Was I dreaming?
Hold on.
It's coming back to me now.
Right before I got sent here
to serve five years
for the robbery I committed,
I picked up that charm.
It was in the washroom
of the holding cell.
But that charm cut my hand,
so I got pissed and sold it to…
What was her name again?
Oh, I think she's called Gwess.
Anyway, I sold it off to her.
And that night…
something caused me to pass out.
I've been held here since.
Have I been bedridden since?
My hand is better too.
Hold on, what just…
Just now, I peeled off
this sticker from my palm.
Is my memory okay?
In 1492, Columbus discovers the Americas.
Bugs Bunny's birthday is July 27th.
No, my memory's fine.
What the…
I'm sure I peeled it off just now.
Wait, what? My shoes…
There are…
One, two…
three, four, five, six…
Huh? What?
Ouch!
Ah, five of them? They're back to normal.
Did the high fever cause astigmatism?!
But that sticker just now...
That's the sticker I tossed aside.
No way…
Gross!
-What are you hollering about?
-Keep it down, will you?
It's nothing. Go back to sleep.
Shit.
No.
I didn't get astigmatism from my fever.
I'm definitely touching the shoe,
and I feel its weight.
This sticker…
When I attach it to an object,
the object is duplicated.
Once you peel it,
there's a bit of destruction,
but it merges back into one.
And this sticker…
I know it sounds crazy,
but there's no doubt about it.
It emerged from inside my body!
And
now that I've accepted it,
it's quite useful.
This is awesome.
No point in overthinking it.
This sticker emerges from my palm.
This is reality.
Asshole.
Give me my money back.
What is this…
He left…
He didn't seem to notice it.
I grabbed it without thinking.
This disc…
What does it do?
Your fever has gone down.
You may now return to your cell.
Well, I have a question.
The bathroom janitor.
Is he a model prisoner? What's his--
And what will you do
with that information?
Next!
The janitor inmate?
How the hell should I know?
No idea.
It's not a CD,
but it's shaped like one
and even reflects light like a disc.
But it's soft and elastic.
Also,
I saw another disc on his face.
There were two of these on him.
What's this? It's projecting something.
The money I took from the sick inmates.
They're mine now.
All 5,000 dollars.
No one will ever find them here.
This image…
McQueen.
Would you like to cooperate
as my partner?
McQueen!
What did I just see?
It's as if I was watching
someone's memory!
I heard…
you've been sneaking around
asking about me.
I've stalked before,
but I've never been stalked by a woman.
Yes, this is a first.
And who the hell are you?
I saw
those discs sticking out of your face!
Discs?
What?
I can't remember a thing! What discs?
I'm such a loser!
I can't remember a thing!
What got you crying all of a sudden?
You took my money at the infirmary.
Just this morning!
Money? That's right.
I had a huge sum of money,
and I hid it somewhere.
But…
I forgot where I hid it!
Hey, are you all right?
Are you messing with me?
Did you just ask if I'm okay?
How nice!
It's been ages since
I last spoke with a woman!
No, it's a first.
I've never had a heartfelt conversation
with a woman before.
I'm in bliss right now.
I hope I can spend the rest of my life
with a wonderful lady like you someday.
What the hell?
But that'll never happen.
I'm pathetic, aren't I?
Yes, I'm trash.
I want to die.
What…
What the hell are you doing?
What is this?
This thing!
STAND NAME: FREEWAY THRU HELL
STAND MASTER: THUNDER MCQUEEN
McQueen…
You have pure evil within you.
You have no malice or animosity.
You think you don't inconvenience others.
You victimize yourself,
and you have no interest in others,
yet you're always wishing
for someone to save you.
But that's precisely why
you are the worst.
You drag others down with you.
You are the purest form of evil.
I really like you, McQueen.
If you ever find my enemies
within these prison walls,
you will surely clean them out
and take care of them for me.
Dammit! He hanged himself...
and now my neck...
Someone!
Someone help!
I'm passing out...
Maybe if I bring his body down,
my body will be lowered too?
Sticker.
He has strange powers like I do.
So there are others like me!
Dammit.
Just who the hell are you?
Why did you hang yourself?
Did you save me?
I owe my life to you.
Who the hell are you?
What do you want from me?
I know you have some sort of ability!
An ability?
I don't know what you mean.
But don't worry.
I won't do that again.
I can see clearly now.
And I owe you for saving my life.
I'll repay you someday.
Don't worry about that.
It was nothing.
What the hell are you doing?
What is this?
Those scars…
He must have suicidal tendencies!
And he himself is unaware of his ability.
This is bad.
I'm even in the same position as him.
Dammit, I'm farther away from him now.
You bastard!
Dammit!
The disc!
I don't understand what's going on,
but it's got to do something
with those discs!
Let me die.
I said I'd repay you,
but a guy like me
would never be able to do that
because I'm trash!
I don't want anything to do with you!
Stay away from me, or I'll kill you!
Please do!
I wouldn't mind being killed
by a beautiful woman like you!
It looked like she picked up
a disc from the bathroom floor.
For some reason,
I think it belonged to me.
I wonder if she'll give it back.
No, probably not.
Let me pass!
I have permission to leave.
I'm returning to the women's prison.
Dammit!
I need to get as far away
from that psycho as possible.
I need to get back
to my cell.
I knew it.
So your powers have awakened.
I'll tell you one thing.
That power that awakened within you…
It's called a Stand ability.
Stand abilities are drawn
to one another like gravity.
It happens without reason.
That's why you ran into that janitor.
Why is there a kid?!
You picked up and sold Jolyne's charm.
That's why she told me
to keep an eye on you.
You know Jolyne?
What happened to her?
Our enemy has the ability to steal souls.
We are looking for a soul he stole.
A soul?
The culprit's name is Pale Snake.
Please tell me anything you know.
Soul?
Could you be talking about this disc?
That disc!
This belongs to the janitor.
What's the significance of these discs?
Did he have two discs?
Two discs? He did.
A memory disc and a Stand disc.
Discs come in pairs.
Two discs make up a soul.
If only we can get his other disc,
we may be able to learn
the identity of Pale Snake!
Hell no…
No way!
It's still following me around.
Dammit! I thought I got far enough.
What's happening?
Electricity! That bastard!
He's electrocuting himself!
It... It stopped.
Electrical resistance.
You can't kill a person just by sending
100 volts of electricity on human skin.
We have electrical resistance.
That's why it stopped.
His suicide attempt failed.
But…
if he wants to electrocute himself again,
he'd be looking around
for some saline solution right about now.
Saline solution would increase
conductivity to almost 100 percent.
Electricity can pierce
and burn the heart completely.
Saline solution?
They are used as IVs and disinfectants.
There's a bunch by the infirmary!
I can't go any further.
There are too many inmates by the stairs!
I'll beat him up and take his other disc.
That's my only way!
Stop! Don't do this!
Look at my left arm!
It's a little burnt, just like your arm.
You have obtained a strange ability.
Every suicide attempt
is reflected onto me!
Don't think about suicide!
There are lots of fun
and lucky things in life too!
Four years ago,
I was only cleaning.
Cleaning the shotgun in my apartment.
But for some reason, the gun was loaded.
The gun accidentally fired.
I live on the tenth floor.
Just as the gun went off,
a woman jumped to kill herself.
It was like the lottery.
While some win millions of dollars,
I guess sometimes
the exact opposite happens.
She was supposed to
hit the ground and die.
Everyone thought that I aimed at
and killed the woman on the 11th floor.
The judge even called me cold-blooded.
That's the kind of man I am!
Hold on!
Oh, panties.
Has anyone given you panties before?
Wouldn't you feel lucky
if a girl gave you her panties?
You're going through
tough times right now.
But imagine.
If a girl gives you panties,
that means lucky things can happen
even at the worst moment.
Oh, I'm so embarrassed!
But you can have it.
I'll give you the one I got on right now!
You'll really give me your panties?
I keep my promises.
But remember this.
Everyone hates Mondays.
We all hope for
the fun Saturdays to come around.
Not every day is a Monday!
I was arrested on a Saturday.
You're saying nice things to give me hope,
but I bet it's just lip service
to save yourself.
That's not…
You are pretending to be kind
just to get out of this situation.
You don't mean a word you say.
Am I wrong?
That's how everyone always treats me.
Nobody likes trash.
But I'm worse than trash.
My presence is invisible to everyone!
Hold on!
Yes, I'm talking to you
because I don't want to die.
But listen up.
You are being used by Pale Snake.
He's exploiting your mindset!
If you don't think about suicide,
nothing will happen!
You are the one who's being selfish,
you bastard!
You really are a nice person.
How wonderful.
Those words were sincere.
I sure am fortunate.
I ran into such
a beautiful woman before my passing.
Thank you!
If I can die with you…
If I can spend an eternity with you,
then I'm really blessed!
He's evil.
He is, without a doubt,
rotten to his core!
I'm not lonely!
-Here!
-Bastard! Let go of that switch!
That was close.
Too close, dammit!
I managed to attach the sticker.
It'll burn from the sparks of electricity.
Once the sticker burns off,
the copy created with the sticker will…
merge back to one!
Goddammit.
The shock made me remember.
He hid the money he stole, 5,000 dollars.
I'll take it as payment, you little shit.
And then there's Pale Snake.
I went through this because of him.
Just what are you planning?
ERMES COSTELLO, STAND NAME: "SMACK"
I have to go see her. Jolyne…
Jolyne Cujoh.
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter